<resources>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">Very basic gesture nav system only made for the S9+.
        This is a personal project and no other devices/settings are supported.</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">PREF</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="navAreaWidthDescription">Controls how wide the navigation area is.
        The pill will also fill the entire width of the navigation recognition area.</string>
    <string name="navAreaHeightDescription">Controls the height of the navigation area. The entire sensor area is determined by this height.</string>
    <string name="navBarHeightDescription">This controls the display height of the navigation bar.
        This is only for display properties and does not affect the sensor area of the navigation area.</string>
    <string name="navBarRadiusDescription">Changes how round the navigation bar appears. This is only for cosmetic purposes.</string>
    <string name="navAreaXOffsetDescription">Changes how much the navigation area/bar is offset horizontally.
        Normally this value should be 0 because we want the navigation area and bar to be centered.</string>
    <string name="navAreaYOffsetDescription">Controls how much the navigation area/bar is offset from the bottom of the screen.
        This is used to offset the changes from overscan hiding the navigation bar.</string>
    <string name="vibrationIntensityDescription">Changes how intense the vibration is when an action is performed.</string>
    <string name="vibrationLengthDescription">Changes the length of the vibration of when an action is performed.</string>
    <string name="timeDurationBeforeFadeDescription">The length of time before the navigation bar fades out.
        This is in ms and is used to prevent screen burn in.</string>
    <string name="navAreaPrimaryColorDescription">This determines the primary color of the navigation bar.</string>
    <string name="navAreaSecondaryColorDescription">This determines the outline color of the navigation bar.</string>
</resources>
